# **Dominic Jackson**

GitHub: github.com/domjacks1
Website: domjacks1.github.io

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/dominic-j18

### **Summary**

Software Engineer with hands-on experience with DevSecOps working on large infrastructure projects for high-profile external clients. Enthusiastic team-player working in Agile SCRUM teams who likes to take ownership of products and help solve customer problems.

#### Highlight Skills

```
* Angular.js, HTML5, CSS, Bootstrap

* Java, Spring, Node.js

* JUnit, Cucumber, TestInfra, Selenium

* Ansible, Vagrant, Docker, VMWare, STRIDE

* MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL

* JIRA, Bamboo, Confluence, Bitbucket, Hipchat

* Redhat 6/7, CentOS 7

* Apache NiFi, Kafka, Zookeeper, RabbitMQ, Splunk, ELK
```

### **Experience**

BT Security - Software Engineer - (2016 - Present)

Completed two year Graduate Scheme. Worked on two projects for external clients, one based in London and one based on a client site in Greater Manchester.

SSiD Sheffield University - Web Support Assistant (2014 - 2016)

Part-time role whilst studying. Responsibilities were assisting with web-change requests using a CMS, updating the core student facing pages and managing UX testing for University web pages.

BT Security - Research & Development Intern (2015)

Twelve week Cyber Security summer internship between my second and third year of studying. Responsibilities included completing an R&D project based on Wi-Fi and Bluetooth vulnerabilities.

BAE Systems - Work Experience Student (2010)

Two week shadowing opportunity during High School at their Warton site with the Weapons Integration and Flight Operations teams.

### **Education**

University of Sheffield - 2013-2016

Computer Science BSc - First Class Honours

Cardinal Newman College - 2011-2013

Computing - A, Maths - B, General Studies - B, Physics - C

#### Courses

QA Linux System Administration (QALXSA2)

1 week course learning topics ranging from the Linux Kernel all the way to networking and security.

QA Commercial and Financial Awareness (ZBTFCA)

2 day Performance Based Learning course designed to provide an opportunity to begin to understand what commercial and financial awareness means in the real world.

BT Leadership Launchpad

4-day residential event geared towards development of strengths i.e. Team, Ownership, Networking and Learning. Completed Discovery Insights profile to guide training.

## **Volunteering & Awards**

Made in Sheffield - Coding Mentor

Local Community run scheme to introduce school children to STEM topics. I volunteered as a Software Engineering mentor and helped teach the kids basic coding skills.

**IBM Challenge Award** 

University award for completing the best group project. We helped a start-up company create a tool to quickly and efficiently gather feedback on the company and allowed them to suggest continuous improvements.